Nice to meet you. Hello. I am 18 years old, from Kyoto, Japan, and my name is Yamashita Suzuki.
I came to Kyoto today. I came to a place called Heian Jingu Shrine, but it was my first time. Actually, it is my first time.
Is it a garden in Heian Jingu Shrine? It's a garden. I'm going to the garden now.
Wow. Wow. I've come to a place where the sound of water is beautiful.
Birds. Birds. Birds.
There are birds.
Well, it's a good shot. Isn't it a great shot? Here.
Wow, yay! It looks like Kyoto, doesn't it? Very Kyoto.
There's a thing where you have to cross this pond so you don't fall in.
If you fall in, you'll get Santa Kinami.
Oh!
Do you see how it looks like? It looks like this.
I'm crossing it right now.
Scary. I'm really scared.
Okay, okay, okay, I'm done.
I crossed with all my heart.
I've been feeling for the little fish since a while ago.
We are here.
We are now at the Kamogawa River in Kyoto.
My favorite foods are ramen and spicy food.
I'm pretty particular about ramen, too.
I like tonkotsu thin noodles.
I eat quite a lot of ramen.
I have eaten five bowls of ramen in the past.
I also like very spicy food.
I have never thought of them as spicy.
I would like to try something extremely spicy once.
I have always loved the Sakamichi group.
I go to their live concerts and sightseeing.
My other hobby is collecting live photo albums.
My hobby is to collect live photos, so I buy a lot of goods and so on.
They have helped me a lot.
When Sakurazaka46 appeared on a singing show, I fell in love with Honoo Tamura at first sight.
I fell in love with Honoo Tamura at first sight.
I fell in love with Honoo Tamura when she appeared on a singing show, and I fell in love with Sakurazaka 46 from there.
I saw their performances on TV and at their live shows.
She was so cool.
I know her usual atmosphere and I can see the different aura she has when she dances.
I was really attracted to their different aura and atmosphere when they danced.
I was really attracted to the different aura and atmosphere of the dancers.
I wondered if I could be like them.
So I auditioned.
If you hadn't joined Sakurazaka, what kind of work would you have done?
What kind of work would you have done if you had not joined Sakurazaka?
I was asked the question, "If you had not joined Sakurazaka, what kind of work would you have been doing?
I have always dreamed of becoming a police officer or a virtual prefectural police officer.
I wanted to work for a job where I could help others in the future.
I wanted to work for someone in the future.
I thought that being an idol was the same as helping people.
I thought that idol work is the same in the sense that I can help people.
I myself have been helped a lot by idols.
I have been helped a lot by idols.
So I'm really trying to do my best now.
I think I'm about 2 months behind everyone else.
I think I'm about two months behind everyone else, but I've been working together with everyone up until now.
I've been taking lessons together with everyone.
I've been taking lessons with everyone.
I have been taking lessons with everyone, but there are not many things that I can participate in.
I had a lot of hard time, but I've been able to participate in the lessons with everyone.
It was very hard for me.
From now on, I will be able to work with everyone without worrying about
I am very happy to be able to work with everyone without worrying about the delay.
I would like to do my best in the 11 years of my third term.
I will do my best from now on.
I will do my best from now on, so please give me your support.